Dana Bartley

Bowling Green, KY 42101 danabartley8_7hp@indeedemail.com 270-535-3272

I have worked in varies professional business industries for over 27 years. I have gathered lots of experience by working in several business departments ranging from accounts payable, accounts receivable, auditing and human resources. I enjoy data entry, working with accounts payables and receivables and helping others resolve issues. I want to continue utilizing my knowledge and job experience.

- Positive attitude
 Detailed oriented
- Quick learner Mature Employee

Work Experience

Account Specialist

Lifeskills - Bowling Green, KY December 2019 to Present

The responsibilities that I have is daily recording wires and make journal entries into the AS400 system and enter daily cash receipts for three accounts. I am responsible for entering all journal entries into the system as well as balancing accounts and billing for specific cost centers to the State of Kentucky. I create pass-thru Purchase Requisitions for State Funding/Grant Programs and create PRS for Lifeskills financial department.

Financial Accounting Clerk

Gardant Management Solutions - Bourbonnais, IL July 2016 to December 2019

My responsibilities are to review, ensure accurate coding from the Business Office Manager and approve invoices through avidxchange timely. Avidxchange is an on-line A/P & Payment automation system, paperless approval process. It is my responsibility making sure that the chart of accounts is updated and accurate. I have roughly 37 Assisted Senior Living Communities that I review and approve their accounts payable invoices.

Accounts Specialist

Chandler Property Management - Bowling Green, KY April 2003 to April 2016

I processed all vendor invoices for the Chandler Property Management owners' portfolio and ensuring that payments were paid timely and accurately. I reconciled their credit card payments against the receipts from the employees. I helped with month and year end monthly cash reports and distributions for owners of the varies communities. I filed invoices and check stubs and then boxed and stored at year end.

I provided accurate accounts receivable data entries for past and current tenants that

helped maintain great relationships between our tenants and the staff. I held the responsibility of making accurate and timely bank deposits in person and by remote deposit and ensured bills were paid timely.

- I acquired the knowledge to prioritize duties to meet job requirements.
- I learned Yardi Genesis in depth to make my job more functional which saved payroll hours for Chandler Property Management.
- I formed business relations with tenants/bank personnel/vendors/collections which were valuable in marketing and promoting the business in a positive manner.

Accounts Payable Clerk

CHANDLER PROPERTY MANAGEMENT - Bowling Green, KY April 2003 to 2016

Chandler Property Management has built a solid reputation of providing the highest quality homes, townhouses, duplexes, and apartment homes in Bowling Green, KY. CPM serves the needs of over 1200 customers with approximately 1000 apartment homes in the Bowling Green area

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT

Brantley Appraisal Company - Bowling Green, KY January 2002 to April 2003

I assisted Mr. Brantley and his associate in preparing appraisal reports and generated building/home square footage drawings using the Appraisal Tool software. I managed the deposits and payables for all appraisals and also 60+ rental units that Mr. Brantley owned.

I help researched his previous appraisals and updated for current and future use.

- I learned to use Appraisal Tool Software to help support the appraisers.
- I was taught how to search for property comps and used that knowledge in providing this information for the appraisal reports.
- I self-taught the use of a dictation recorder to help finalized the appraisal report and mailed completed report to clients.
- I educated myself on how to look up deeds/PVA and to use this information on the appraisal reporting.

Administrative Assistant

BRANTLEY APPRISAL COMPANY - Bowling Green, KY January 2002 to April 2003

Real estate appraisal, property valuation or land valuation is the practice of developing an opinion of the value of real property, usually its Market Value.

Accounts Payable Auditor

MINIT MART FOODS, LLC - Bowling Green, KY June 1990 to April 2001

MMF was founded in 1967 by Fred Higgins and his father, Ralph Higgins, who had previously owned the first Stuckey's franchise in the country. In 1988 Minit Mart expanded its business to Tennessee when it acquired 19 Bread Box convenience stores there. During this time, Minit Mart continued to build on its reputation as a pioneer in the convenience store industry by adding delis, game machines and videotape rentals in its established

stores. The volume of the operation was in excess of \$250 million dollars annually with approximately 1,200 employees.

Benefit Coordinator

MINIT MART FOODS, LLC 1998 to 2001

I helped administer the worker compensation and liability insurance programs. I preserved the records for eligible employees for educational assistance. I helped with the weekly payroll in auditing the payroll report and ensured hours were recorded accurately and employees were paid correctly. I also aided in the cash management department.

- I obtained the knowledge of worker's comp and liability insurance procedure.
- I learned the process of education assistance program and eligibility which helped the eligible employee extend their education.
- I ensured that all eligible employees were informed about the annual open enrollment policy and forms were completed on time.
- I helped with the administration of payroll and cash handling.

Lottery and Money Order Coordinator

MINIT MART FOODS, LLC 1995 to 1998

- I reconciled money orders in the cash management (CM) department.
- I reconciled Kentucky lottery invoices and payoffs in the CM department.

Accounts payable auditor

MINIT MART FOODS, LLC 1990 to 1995

- I learned how to read and understand the stores' daily cash report.
- I was taught the process on payables, vendors and researching.

Education

ASSOCIATE DEGREE in BUSINESS

WESTERN KENTUCKY UNIVERSITY - Bowling Green, KY

Skills

- Accounts Payable (10+ years)
- Quickbooks (2 years)
- Outlook (7 years)
- MS Office (5 years)
- Billing (10+ years)
- Financial Accounting
- Journal Entries
- Yardi

- Property Management
- General Ledger Reconciliation
- Accounts Receivable